[{"answer": "Well I am actually going to have a secretary and I get to do the interview", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, and now someone's going to be taking messages for me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Ah, she keeps it in my apartment for when she comes up from that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How fast was she walking?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No. I think it's my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well we could ..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What can I say? I'm ... I'm good at what I do.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Yes, I think I do.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What would he be doing wearing your jacket", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Maybe you could have sex with her again and then take it back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "All right, all right. I'm sorry", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "She supports her whole family.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, In fact, her mother is in the hospital right now. It's some kind of a Diverticulitis.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Is that a fact my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I had a bout of that myself one time", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, come on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Now? ", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, I, I need to see that ticket", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, but this is different. Those fur storage warehouses are huge. You can't, get anything without a number", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes, I tell you, Mr. my friend..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, where's my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm going out.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Pretty good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well all you gotta do is tell my friend to give me my money back, and you'll get your ticket", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, see the thing of it is, I'm in a bit of an awkward position here. Because, uhh, I don't want to get in between you two guys but ... I need a dr", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, yeah all right, well uh ... tell you what I will do Bania", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah all right, well uh ... tell you what I will do Bania", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You want to go to my friend's, I'll take you to my friend's", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Can we go back to my friend's", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Secretary.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Twice? I wanna go twice", "qsentId": 36}]